This big boy is so lovable.
This big boy.
No wonder he's so tall.
Who did he get it from?
Such a big guy.
Y'know?
Let me try.
Put your hands up. What hands?
I don't have hands.
I've used my arms since I was little.
Honestly, I can't win this one.
And none of you will win either.
I won't wear this sleeping bag anymore.
I'll guard here and see who gets past me.
I just love watching He fall in love.
I just love watching this kind of stuff.
What exactly are you saying OK to?
Who let you change my destination?
I'm the big baby.
Shoot me if you have the guts.
What the hell is this gun for?
What use are you?
You're completely useless.
Always acting tough and bullying us.
He just says whatever works for him.
You can get out now.
Friend.
Wifey.
Where are your things?
Should I go lead the way?
Guys.
Of course.
You gotta lead.
Don't disappear on me.
Nobody's here.
Let's keep moving forward.
Let me check if there's any danger.
OK, turn off the lights.
Come on.
Is something moving?
It's fine.
Holy crap.
Now listen to me.
Here's the situation.
I'm at the very front.
So you guys just follow me.
Just keep moving forward, don't worry.
Because I'm still in front of you.
It's fine.
Come on, come on.
It's fine, it's fine.
The God of Destiny always favors me.
I've unlocked it, fam.
We can help you guys.
For example.
I'll carry it on my back.
Right?
I'll do squats.
Thirteen, fourteen.
Hey.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Let's go, go.
Take it slow.
We'll just look for the shoes.
Right.
Lord Egg.
I'm so eager to protect the princess...
I'd die for her anytime, anywhere.
It's okay, it's okay.
Lean on me.
Ah.
I really am protecting you!
You protected me.
Bro.
Can't bring him.
Can't bring you.
Take one.
Oh.
I brought it for you.
Thanks, bro.
I brought you the smelly stick. Come on.
Take this, take this, take this.
Wait, you protected me.
Bro.
I-I-I-I mean...
Yeah.
I'm a blade.
A blade doesn't need a brain.
A blade just needs to be sharp.
First of all,
you're sure the body is under the bed.
Okay.
Then if I were feeling guilty,
would I invite four people to my room
to sit on top of the dead body?
Am I that bold
when I have a guilty conscience?
So right now, as I see it,
I'm quite suspicious of you.
You definitely won't find someone who
has both.
Nor will you find anyone who has neither.
Because to me, your motives are average.
That sticker was put back on.
Who told you it was put back on?
Because two layers are stuck together.
How do you know when it was stuck on?
It's just a guess.
What's the basis for your guess?
Why is it that you haven't been into
the mortuary?
How do you prove you've never been there?
I must take responsibility for my words.
It's fine.
I don't buckle under pressure.
Got it?
Pressure me all you want.